...and if I stop talking about it
then I'm just...
(Bernadette:)Just what?
(Howard:)Just plain old Howard Wolowitz again.
(Howard:)Plain old Howard Wolowitz
is the best guy I know.
- You're just saying that.
- No, I'm not.
(Bernadette:)I married him. On purpose.
(Bernadette:)Come here.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
(Penny(emerging from Tardis):)Nothing to see here,
just sexy police business.
(Leonard:)Just explaining the theory of relativity.
(Bernadette:)Twice.
(Bernadette:)Hey, what you watching?
(Howard:)I don't know.
Raj sent me some video of Buzz Aldrin.
(Buzz(on video, handing Halloween candy to children):)Here you go, it's a Milky Way.
The Milky Way is a galaxy in space.
(Buzz(on video, handing Halloween candy to children):)I've been in space.
(Buzz(on video, handing Halloween candy to children):)Here's a Mars bar.
(Buzz(on video, handing Halloween candy to children):)I'm an astronaut.
And this one's a MoonPie.
(Buzz(on video, handing Halloween candy to children):)I walked on the Moon.
(Buzz(on video, handing Halloween candy to children):)What have you done?
(Howard:)Okay, I get it.